<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Website on Jack Gregory</title>
    <link>/tags/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Website on Jack Gregory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2022 Jack Gregory</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Google Analytics on hugo-apéro</title>
      <link>/blog/google-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/google-analytics/</guid>
      <description>TL;DRIn this blog, I summarize the steps necessary to set up Google Analytics on a Hugo-Apéro website.
IntroductionGoogle Analytics is a useful tool for measuring and understanding engagement with your personal website. In my experience, it is probably the most painless method for accessing detailed tracking data for a Hugo site. Helpfully, most Hugo themes come with it pre-installed through an internal template.
In this blog, I&amp;rsquo;ll outline the two steps necessary to configure Google Analytics for your Hugo-Apéro website:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to restrict access to a hugo-apéro website on GitHub Pages ...</title>
      <link>/blog/hugo-apero-private/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hugo-apero-private/</guid>
      <description>TL;DRIn this blog, I summarize the steps necessary to adapt the deployment of a Hugo-Apéro website to GitHub Pages while keeping either the content or the full website code private.
IntroductionThis is a followup to my companion blog post titled: How to setup hugo-apéro on GitHub Pages. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for details on how to setup your Hugo-Apéro website from scratch, I would recommend starting there.
In the previous post, the setup resulted in a public GitHub repository for your website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to setup hugo-apéro on GitHub Pages ...</title>
      <link>/blog/hugo-apero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hugo-apero/</guid>
      <description>TL;DRIn this blog, I summarize the steps necessary to adapt the deployment of a Hugo-Apéro website to GitHub Pages. I also discuss how to use git submodules to include a theme dynamically.
IntroductionHugo-Apéro is a Hugo theme for publishing websites using the blogdown package within R. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m using to publish my personal site here!
Even if you&amp;rsquo;ve never used Hugo or blogdown previously, the setup is fairly straightforward.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
