<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Jack Gregory</title>
    <link>/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Jack Gregory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2022 Jack Gregory</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to setup hugo-apéro on GitHub Pages ...</title>
      <link>/blog/hugo-apero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hugo-apero/</guid>
      <description>TL;DRIn this blog, I summarize the steps necessary to adapt the deployment of a Hugo-Apéro website to GitHub Pages. I also discuss how to use git submodules to both shield content and include a theme dynamically.
IntroductionHugo-Apéro is a Hugo theme for publishing websites using the blogdown package within R. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m using to publish my peronsal site here!
Even if you&amp;rsquo;ve never used Hugo or blogdown previously, the setup is fairly straightforward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GII Economy Briefs</title>
      <link>/project/gii-briefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/gii-briefs/</guid>
      <description>ObjectiveTo internalize and automatize the production of the Global Innovation Index (GII) economy briefs.
DescriptionIn addition to the ranking and report, the GII launch also includes the release of the economy briefs. The briefs summarize each economy&amp;rsquo;s innovation performance for the specific report year. They tailor material from the report and the economy profiles to provide insights specific to each ranked economy within the GII. A sample brief for Australia from the GII 2022 report can be seen here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GII Data Pipeline</title>
      <link>/project/gii-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/gii-data/</guid>
      <description>ObjectiveTo transition the Global Innovation Index (GII) from a disjointed data collection and quality control process to an industry-standard, cloud-based pipeline that is collaborative, integrated, reproducible, standardized, secure and documented.
DescriptionThe high-level workflow of the GII can be grouped into three phases:
Data; Analysis; and, Output. Figure 1 outlines these phases along with their constituent steps.
Figure 1: High-level GII workflowThis project focuses on the Data phase, where we collect, clean and audit all data necessary for the construction of the Index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GII Economy Profiles</title>
      <link>/project/gii-profiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/gii-profiles/</guid>
      <description>ObjectiveTo internalize and automatize the production of the Global Innovation Index (GII) economy profiles.
DescriptionOne of the main components of the GII report is the economy profiles. The profiles provide an overview of each economy&amp;rsquo;s performance within the GII for the specific report year. They summarize model output, highlight outdated and missing data, and identify indicator strengths and weaknesses. The profiles for the GII 2022 can be seen here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
