<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WIPO on Jack Gregory</title>
    <link>/categories/wipo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in WIPO on Jack Gregory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2022 Jack Gregory</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/wipo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intangible assets owned by all listed companies grew to $74 trillion in 2021</title>
      <link>/blog/intangible-assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/intangible-assets/</guid>
      <description>Concurrent with the digital revolution, intangible assets&amp;mdash;such as R&amp;amp;D, intellectual property, brands, software, databases, organizational assets and skills&amp;mdash;have grown in importance. They are now the cornerstone of any vibrant innovation ecosystem. As such, intangible assets should be part of any measure gauging the success of corporate and national innovation ecosystems.
The Global Innovation Index (GII) 2022 includes novel data quantifying corporate intangible assets worldwide. This comes in support of a broader effort at the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO) to better understand and value intangible assets&amp;mdash;see, for example, the recent High-Level Conversation on Intangible Asset Finance of WIPO’s IP and Innovation Ecosystems Sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Innovation Index 2022</title>
      <link>/talk/gii22-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/gii22-launch/</guid>
      <description>NotesPresented results as a member of the WIPO Secretariat and a member of the Global Innovation Index (GII) team.
OverviewThe 2022 edition of the GII tracks the most recent global innovation trends against the background of an ongoing COVID-19 pandemic, slowing productivity growth and other evolving challenges. It reveals the most innovative economies in the world, ranking the innovation performance of around 132 economies while highlighting innovation strengths and weaknesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GII Economy Briefs</title>
      <link>/project/gii-briefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/gii-briefs/</guid>
      <description>ObjectiveTo internalize and automatize the production of the Global Innovation Index (GII) economy briefs.
DescriptionIn addition to the ranking and report, the GII launch also includes the release of the economy briefs. The briefs summarize each economy&amp;rsquo;s innovation performance for the specific report year. They tailor material from the report and the economy profiles to provide insights specific to each ranked economy within the GII. A sample brief for Australia from the GII 2022 report can be seen here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GII Data Pipeline</title>
      <link>/project/gii-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/gii-data/</guid>
      <description>ObjectiveTo transition the Global Innovation Index (GII) from a disjointed data collection and quality control process to an industry-standard, cloud-based pipeline that is collaborative, integrated, reproducible, standardized, secure and documented.
DescriptionThe high-level workflow of the GII can be grouped into three phases:
Data; Analysis; and, Output. Figure 1 outlines these phases along with their constituent steps.
Figure 1: High-level GII workflowThis project focuses on the Data phase, where we collect, clean and audit all data necessary for the construction of the Index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GII Economy Profiles</title>
      <link>/project/gii-profiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/gii-profiles/</guid>
      <description>ObjectiveTo internalize and automatize the production of the Global Innovation Index (GII) economy profiles.
DescriptionOne of the main components of the GII report is the economy profiles. The profiles provide an overview of each economy&amp;rsquo;s performance within the GII for the specific report year. They summarize model output, highlight outdated and missing data, and identify indicator strengths and weaknesses. The profiles for the GII 2022 can be seen here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
